wisdom-soft.com 2014-06-30

# Wisdom-soft

AutoScreenRecorder

ScreenHunter

MotionStudio

MotionGIF

Downloads

Buy NOW

Prices

How to Order

Company Licenses

Order FAQ

Support Center

FAQ

Support Blog

Site Map

News

User Comments

Awards

Tell Friends

Mailing List

Distribution

|     
|  |  Products   
---  
 AutoScreenRecorder  
 ScreenHunter  
 MotionStudio  
 MotionGIF  
    
Order   
 Buy NOW!  
 Prices  
 How to Order  
    
Download & Support  
 Downloads  
 Support Center  
 FAQ  
 Blog  
 Distribution  
    
Community  
 Latest News  
 Awards & Reviews  
 User Comments  
 Mailing List  
 Tell Friends  
 About Us  

|  |  **Privacy and Data Security**

At Wisdom-soft, your right to privacy and data security is a primary concern. That's why, when you visit Wisdom-soft.com, we help you maintain control over your personal data on the Internet. 

**Wisdom-soft only asks for specific types of personal information **

In a few areas on our Web site and online customer support tools, we ask you to provide information that will enable us to enhance your site visit, to assist you with purchase and technical support issues or to follow up with you after your visit. It is completely optional for you to participate. 

For example, we request information from you when you: 

  1. Register on Wisdom-soft.com 

  2. Request a quote 

  3. Place an order 

  4. Provide feedback in an online survey 

  5. Request e-mail notification of your order status 

  6. Subscribe to a newsletter or a mailing list 

  7. Fill out a support request

Information we may request includes your name, e-mail address, phone number, address, type of business, credit card details, customer preference information, customer number and service tag number, as well as other similar personal information.  Wisdom-soft only uses your personal information for verifying registration status.

The information you provide will be kept confidential and used to support your customer relationship with Wisdom-soft. Among other things, we want to help you quickly find information on Wisdom-soft.com and alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new products and services from Wisdom-soft. Agents or contractors of Wisdom-soft who have access to your personal information and prospect information are required to keep the information confidential and not use it for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for Wisdom-soft. Wisdom-soft may enhance or merge your information collected at its site with data from third parties for purposes of marketing products or services to you. 

In addition, Wisdom-soft may be required to disclose personal information in connection with law enforcement, fraud prevention, regulation, and other legal action or if Wisdom-soft reasonably believes it is necessary to do so to protect Wisdom-soft, its customers, or the public. **

Mailing List

** You can opt-out of Wisdom-soft's mailing list at any time.

Periodically, we may send you information about our various products and services, or other products and services we feel may be of interest to you. Wisdom-soft will not disclose your personal information to any outside organization for its use in marketing without your consent.

Information regarding you (such as name, address and phone number) or your order and the products you purchase will not be given or sold to any outside organization for its use in marketing or solicitation without your consent. Your information may be shared with agents or contractors of Wisdom-soft for the purpose of performing services for Wisdom-soft.   
  
---|---  
  
* * *
